好了 坦白说... 我不擅长约会
Okay, so cards on the table... I'm not that great at dating.
我和前任未婚夫高中起就在一起
My ex-fiancé and I were together since high school,
所以对于约会几乎是菜鸟一只
so I just haven't had a ton of experience at it.
我室友说应该把约会当成游戏
My roommate says you should treat dating as a game.
- 你在干什么? - 我在和他说话
- What are you doing? - I'm talking to this guy.
不是 你为什么说那些话? 好无趣
No, why are you saying what you're saying? It's boring.
什么? 哪里无趣了
What? It's not boring.
抱歉 我朋友要为她的无趣道个歉
I'm sorry. My friend wants to apologize for her boringness.
我不想为我的无趣道歉
I do not want to apologize for my boringness.
为了聊表歉意 她会展示她的马铃薯
To make up for it, she'll show you her taters.
- 我的什么? - 你懂的 你的行李架啊
- My what? - You know, your rack.
枪啊 马克杯啊之类的花哨玩意儿
Your guns. Your geegaws. Your jilk mugs.
看吧? 多无趣
See? So boring.
一周前
好了 伍悦 决定时间到
Okay, May, it's decision time.
你只能从这三个先生中选两个
You can only choose two of these three gentlemen
参加下周的终极抉择
to be in next week's finale.
究竟花落谁家?
Who's it gonna be?
除了与癌症作斗争 这真是我平生
This is the hardest thing I've ever done,
最困难的决定了
besides beat cancer.
你好坚强 伍悦!
You're so strong, May!
谬赞 肖恩
Thank you, Sean.
杰克森...
Jackson...
- 嘿 哦! - 耶!
- Hey-o! - Yeah!
你会接受我的黄金弹簧吗?
Will you accept my golden spring?
当然
Absolutely.
她没选肖恩我真是太开心了
I am so glad that she didn't pick Sean.
噢 我也是 他真是个马屁精
Oh, me, too. He's such a kiss-ass.
你好坚强 伍悦!
"You're so strong, May!"
谁会说那种话?
Who says that?
# 肖恩好无聊 #
# Sean is so lame #
啊 你们还在看"春满五月"?
Ugh. You guys are still watching "Spring Into May"?
难看死了
That show sucks.
詹姆斯对节目主持人超级挑剔
James is super judgy about TV hosts.
看看那小丑
Look at that clown.
我主持的比他好多了
I'm a way better host than he is.
别转台 "春满五月"马上回来
Stay tuned. "Spring Into May" will be right back.
你们应该看过我在比利时
You guys should have seen the dating show
主持的相亲节目
I just hosted in Belgium.
情侣们转啊转
And the lovers are spinning.
德尔椎科 你准备迎接
Diedrick, are you ready for your chance
超乎想象的诱惑了么?
at unimaginable lust?
当然!
Ya!
太棒了!
Wonderbaar!
啊 真好喝 总是这么独一无二
Ahh. Great taste. Always one-of-a-kind.
虽说节目有点乱七八糟
It was a little all over the place.
我是说 那些... 转盘有点危险
I mean, the... the wheels were dangerous.
但我有些绝妙的想法
But I had some really good ideas.
如果制片人肯听我的话...
If the producers had just listened to me...
- 闭嘴! - 节目开始了!
- Quiet! - It's back on!
... 然后只剩二十四人 十四人...
... Then down to 24, then 14...
嗯!
Mm!
哦 呼! 啊
Oh, yeah. Whoo! Whoa.
克洛伊 我们正在看节目
Chloe, we're trying to watch something.
而我在上某人啊
And I am trying to do someone.
少看点傻乎乎的相亲节目吧
Now stop watching these stupid dating shows
来玩嘛阿朱 出去钓凯子
and get in the game, June. Go out and meet somebody.
我是很有原则的
I have very tough criteria.
对象不能是工作场合 健身馆认识的
He can't be from your work or your gym,
同公寓的邻居也不行
or live in your building.
我们早不是同事了
We don't work together anymore.
也得没和克洛伊上过床
And he can't be someone that Chloe slept with,
此等好男天下难寻
which is really hard to find.
嘿? 你觉得我怎么想?
Hello? How do you think I feel?
我只和过去没睡过的人上床
I only sleep with guys I haven't slept with before.
我也有焦土政策的
You know my scorched earth policy.
呃 我们其实上过床
Um, we've actually had sex before.
噢 滚出去
Oh. Get out.
这二十四个男人...
These 24 men...
阿朱 纽约男人满山满谷
June, there are tons of guys in New York.
我带你出门钓个去
I'm gonna take you out and help you meet one.
面前就有
Right here.
好男一名
A good one.
我人就在她眼前
I mean, I was right there.
为什么阿朱从没考虑过
Why doesn't June ever consider me
和我约会?
as someone she might wanna date?
兄弟啊 你在她朋友圈里
Dude, you're in the friend zone.
她的原则不包括这条
That's not one of her criteria.
这是条潜规则
That's an unspoken criteria.
我给那个比利时相亲节目出的主意之一
The friend zone was also one of the ideas I had
就是把朋友圈纳进相亲对象里
to improve that Belgian game show that I hosted.
你看嘛 所有参与者把朋友
See, all the contestants would put their friends
归为一类 或者说"朋友圈"
in an area, or "zone."
听起来... 不错 老兄
That sounds... great, man.
是吧?
Right?
好了 我们不是来酒吧坐一整夜
Okay, so we are not here to sit at the bar
大聊特聊卫生棉
and compare tampons all night.
我们是来找男人的
We are here to talk to guys.
别用你那蠢原则做借口
And stop using your stupid criteria
好宅在沙发里度日
as an excuse to lay on the couch
吃吃墨西哥三明治
and eat Mexican sandwiches.
他的鼻孔会鸣笛耶
His nose is whistling.
这男人说起话来就像在生气
This guy looks so angry when he talks.
他的言辞并不气愤 但看起来气疯了
He's not saying angry words, but he looks so mad.
我是说 他明明在谈论彩虹啊
I mean, he's talking about rainbows.
这男的嘴边沾着橘子酱
This guy has orange mouth corners.
他一直在吃邋遢乔三明治
He's been eating a sloppy Joe,
而且没擦过嘴
and he hasn't even wiped his face.
我要帮他擦嘴 速度溜走
I'm just gonna wipe his mouth and get out of here.
你刚可做了件好事
Hey, you just did a good deed there.
- 噢 你看见了? - 哦 是啊
- Oh, you saw that? - Oh, yeah.
我也受不了别人脸上粘着食物
I can't stand it when people have food on their face.
那真的...
It's so...
- 恶心 我懂! - 恶心 我懂!
- disgusting. I know! - Disgusting. I know!
除了我的姑奶奶
Except when it's my great aunt.
她老了 所以我喜欢帮她擦嘴
She's old, so I like helping her wipe her face.
哇 真温馨
Aw, that's sweet.
总之 我是丹尼尔
Anyway, I'm Daniel.
嗨 我是阿朱
Hi, I'm June.
虽这么说略唐突
Okay, this is gonna sound weird,
但你看哈利波特时
but you just like what I imagined
想象的样子一模一样
Harry Potter would look like when I was reading the books.
只是... 成人版本的
Only the... the grown-up man version.
我的父母也被杀了
Both my parents were also killed,
不过不是巫师干的
but not by a wizard.
我开玩笑的 他们都在康奈迪克州...
I'm kidding. They're in Connecticut...
活得好好的
leading very active lives.
我请你喝一杯好吗?
Can I buy you a drink?
好啊 当然 谢谢
Yeah. Sure. Thank you.
哦 老天 说出来你一定不相信
Oh, God, you're never gonna believe this.
好吧
Okay.
不 不是 我刚刚邂逅了一个帅哥
No, no, I think I just met someone.
很帅又打着光棍
He's cute and he's single,
而且跟他的姑奶奶相处融洽
and he has a good relationship with his great aunt.
不错啊 约他出去
Good. Ask him out.
真的吗? 就这么约?
Really? Just like that?
当然 你漂亮可人
Of course. You're gorgeous.
他将成为这儿最幸运的小伙子
He'll be the luckiest guy here.
你记得稍微抹些唇彩
Just touch up your lip gloss a bit.
哦 好 我补一下妆
Yeah. All right. I'll do it.
好
Okay.
嘿 想不想找机会出门逛逛?
Hey, do you wanna go out sometime?
哇 你在约我吗?
Wow. You're asking me out?
是啊 很奇怪吗?
Yeah. Is that weird?
不 不 荣幸之至
No, no. It's awesome.
就是有点奇怪
The only weird thing
一分钟之内有两个姑娘
is that two different girls just asked me out
同时约我
in the span of one minute.
还有谁?
What other girl asked you out?
哦 那个姑娘
Uh, that girl right over there.
你这双小短腿跑的挺快
You walk fast for your leg length.
你答应过帮我钓汉子
You were supposed to be helping me meet a guy,
而不是亲身上阵
not finding one for yourself.
你究竟什么时候去约他的?
When did you even have time to ask him out?
你抹唇彩的时候
When you were putting on your lip gloss.
调虎离山之计
That was a diversion tactic on my part.
说实话你裹得太严实了
Frankly, you were kind of already wearing too much.
为什么要这么捉弄我?
Why would you do that to me?
我就是爱夺人所好
I've always wanted what other people want.
没人要的东西谁稀罕?
You take something that's available... who wants that?
但是从别人那里抢过来...
Take something from someone...
价逾千金
value.
难以置信 这又不是游戏
Unbelievable. This is not a game.
但是可以是哦
But it could be.
唔 詹姆斯一直在那儿坐着吗?
Ooh. James has been sitting in that chair the whole time?
我被你迷死了 詹姆斯
I'm intrigued, James.
你俩可以竞争约会 那位帅哥尊姓大名?
You two could compete for this guy. What's his name?
- 丹尼尔 - 我哪能知道
- Daniel. - No earthly idea.
我来定规则 顺便融入我想用在
I'll set the rules, incorporating the ideas
比利时相亲节目的那点子
that I wanted to use in Belgium.
要是有成效
And if it works,
我来把它包装成电视节目 亲自主持
I'll pitch it as a TV show and host it myself.
不行! 你不能这么玩弄别人的感情
No! You can't toy with a person like that.
再说我永远不会跟克洛伊抢男人
Besides, I would never compete against Chloe for a guy.
她会第一时间跟那个男人上床
The first thing she'd do is just sleep with him.
知己啊
You know it.
好吧 阿朱 鉴于这是事实
Well, June, as it just so happens,
我的规则之一就是前五次约会不准上床
one of my rules is no sex for the first five dates.
这样 克洛伊就不能占便宜了
That way Chloe can't gain an unfair advantage.
嘘
Boo.
换句话说要么我不参与游戏
So basically, either I don't play,
这样克洛伊就会跟丹尼尔上床 我就不能约他了
in which case Chloe sleeps with Daniel and makes him undatable,
要么我参与 还有机会和她约会
or I actually play, and I have a chance to date him.
- 很好 加你了 - 好吧 我不干了
- Great. You're in. - Yeah, well, I'm out.
约五次都不上床还不折磨死我了
No sex for five dates sounds like torture.
太好了 那丹尼尔归我了
Awesome. So I get Daniel.
不行 你想约他? 他是我的 我参加!
No. You want him? He's mine. I'm back in. Value!
完美!
Perfect! Okay.
趁着我们单身 赶紧交往吧
Let's mingle while we're single.
游戏就是这样开始的
That's how the game starts.
我刚刚宣布游戏正式开始了
The game just officially started.
太不明显了
That wasn't clear.
好 游戏的基本规则是这样的
Okay, so here are the basic rules of the game...
不能让丹尼尔知道你们在竞争
Daniel cannot know you're competing for him.
你们每个人可以跟他约会五次 不能发生关系
You will each go on five platonic dates.
你们每个人都会拿到一张中途插一腿牌
You will each get an interruption card,
一张缓冲牌  一张乾坤大扭转牌
a cool-down card, and a monkey wrench card
什么时候都可以用
which can be played at any time.
你还做了卡片?
You had cards made up?
漂亮吧?
Aren't they beautiful?
也不全是我的功劳啦
I can't take all the credit.
复印店的老板娘也出了些好点子
The woman at Kinko's had some great thoughts.
- 有问题 - 请讲
- Question. - Yes.
我们能痛扁卢瑟一顿吗?
Can we punch Luther?
不能 每次约会结束后
No. So at the end of each date,
我会计算出你们跟丹尼尔
I will count out the number of true connection moments
来电的次数
you each have with Daniel.
次数多者胜
Whoever has the most wins the round,
而且可以在下一次约会中
and gets... Beek bucks
使用我们的奖品比克元
to use on their next date.
这是我去年复活节
These are from the Van Der Beek Monopoly set
在范德・比克专卖店做的
I made last easter.
卢瑟 你今天很在状态嘛
Luther, you are on it today.
我昨晚睡得很香哦
I got great sleep last night.
我也想参加 不管是哪个男的
I wanna play. I don't even care who the guy is.
我就是想跟克洛伊做游戏
I just wanna play a game with Chloe.
好啊 多元化 进来吧
Great. Diversity. Get in here.
耶!
Eee! Yes!
- 组个联盟吗? - 不行
- Form an alliance? - No.
好吧 也行
This is great.
第一轮
For the first round,
我需要你们每个人在那张纸上
I need you to write down your ideal date
写下你们理想的约会是什么样的
on that sheet of paper.
这么说呢
So...
阿朱你的第一次约会
for your first date, June,
你要去...去地牢
you will be going... to a dungeon.
等等 我...我没写"地牢"啊
Wait. I... I didn't write down "dungeon."
我写的是"野餐"
I wrote down "picnic."
你和克洛伊要互换选择
You and Chloe are switching dates.
不会吧!
No!
天 太好玩儿了 我是不是很变态?
God. I'm weirdly into this.
我知道整件事很疯狂
I knew the whole thing was crazy,
但是我真的很喜欢丹尼尔
but I really liked Daniel.
我们就在酒吧里聊过几分钟
I mean, we only chatted for a few minutes in the bar,
但是我很久都没有
but I hadn't felt a connection like that
这种来电的感觉了
with someone in a long time.
所以我想我还是去地牢...
So I guess I'm going on a date...
约会吧
In a dungeon.
我公寓里有一个通风口
I have a vent in my apartment
我能听到23号公寓的一切动静
that lets me hear everything going on in apartment 23.
我很纳闷 他们怎么从来没问过我
It's weird they never ask me
我是怎么掌握他们的所有动向的
how I always know what's happening.
或者 我怎么把我的月经周期跟克洛伊调成一样的
Or how I've trained my body to get on Chloe's cycle.
所以 这是一个地牢
So... this is a dungeon.
是
Yeah.
我知道 这儿有点儿诡异
I know, it's... it's kind of weird.
不是 我只是很惊讶你怎么会选这个地方
No. I'm just surprised you chose this place.
惊喜吗?
Good surprised?
更像是
More like
"我为什么要穿休闲鞋来这种地方"式的惊喜
"why did I wear loafers to a dungeon?" surprised.
嘿 想再来点酒吗?
Hey, are you ready for another one?
好的 谢谢
Yes, please.
发卡 发卡 发猴卡
Card. Card. Monkey card.
我出卡打断你的约会
I interrupt your date with cards.
快走开
Get outta here.
丹尼尔和我刚刚来 我可不走
Daniel and I just got here. I am not leaving.
呃 这就是游戏规则啊 阿朱
Um, those are the rules of the game, June.
你想打破游戏规则?
Do you really wanna break the rules of the game?
我不知道游戏规则
I didn't know the rules of the game.
我只是想把那几张牌甩出去然后大喊
I just wanted to slam down the cards and yell.
我讨厌游戏
I hate games.
丹尼尔
Daniel.
克洛伊
Chloe.
哇 在这碰到你可真奇怪
Wow. That is so weird running into you here.
我们不是明天见面吗?
We're seeing each other tomorrow, right?
让我告诉你她有急事
She asked me to tell you she had an emergency.
然后捂着她的嘴和屁股跑出去了
She ran out of here holding her mouth and her butt.
噢天哪
Oh, my God.
不说她啦
Anyway, enough about her.
我在这哪 这算是个约会
I'm here now, and this counts as a date.
还有四次就可以上床了
Only four more until sex.
走一个!
My man!
有点难以预料
It's a little predictable.
就是...很好 但不是特别好
I just... it's good. It's not great.
我觉得我需要把事情白热化
I feel like I need to shake things up, you know?
搞个出乎意料的问题什么的
Throw a curveball at 'em or something.
你说啥?
What are you talking about?
我给阿朱和克洛伊搞的约会游戏的节目啊
Dating show I'm work-shopping with June and Chloe.
我这个节目的点子太棒了
I'm really on to something with this show idea,
只是...好像落了什么
I just... I'm missing something.
你看约会节目 有什么主意吗?
You watch dating shows. Any ideas?
你想让我帮着阿朱约会?
You want me to help set June up on dates?
这种事我是绝对不会干的
That's the exact opposite of something I'd be into.
等等 你还喜欢她吗?
Wait, you still have a crush on her?
没那么长时间吧
It hasn't been that long.
这已经是你最长时间的暗恋了
It's been, like, the longest crush of all time.
从你开始喜欢她起 我都喜欢了十个人了
I've had about ten crushes since yours started.
十一个人
11.
真无聊
This sucks.
野餐是你的主意
This picnic was your idea.
你干嘛只带一个椅子?
Why'd you only bring one chair?
丹尼尔 我不...
Daniel, I don't...
我不知道 丹尼尔
I don't know, Daniel.
你想来点吃的吗?
Do you want some food or something?
威士忌?
Whiskey?
蛋?
An egg?
那就 来个蛋吧
An egg, I guess.
噢
Oh!
老天! 蛋是生的!
God! It's not even hard-boiled!
咋啦?
What?
不管了 这得算是一次约会
Anyway, this counts as a date.
只有三次就可以上床啦
Only three more until sex.
哦 等你搞完之后
Oh, and when you're done,
这把椅子得换到托尼聚会租赁店去
this chair has to be returned to Tony's Party Rentals.
你欠他50块
You owe him 50 bucks.
这价钱跟抢似的
His prices are pretty unreasonable.
好的 姑娘们
Okay, ladies,
游戏进行到现在
now at this point in the game,
你们都没有与丹尼尔有什么实质性的
none of you have scored any true connection moments
进展
with Daniel.
我本来要有的
I would've had one
要是克洛伊没有打断我的约会的话
if Chloe hadn't interrupted my date.
洛冰 你甚至都没有去尝试与丹尼尔见面
Now, Robin, you haven't even tried to meet Daniel yet.
呃 我知道
Uh, I know.
身边男孩子太多了
I've got dudes comin' out of my ears.
这太荒唐了
This is ridiculous.
我是唯一一个真正喜欢他的
I am the only one who likes this guy.
那么 现在就有一个机会让你去证明的
Well, now here is your chance to prove it.
下一个挑战就是提问环节
Our next challenge is a quiz round,
由Diet Dr.pepper赞助支持
sponsored by Diet Dr. Pepper.
Dr.pepper最喜欢赞助我了
Dr. Pepper loves everything I get involved with.
詹姆斯・范德・ 比克 和 Diet Dr. Pepper...
James Van Der Beek and Diet Dr. Pepper...
D.d.p., J.v.b.
D.D.P., J.V.B.
这项挑战是为考察你们中的谁
This challenge is designed to determine
和丹尼尔在一起最有头脑
which of you has the brains to be with Daniel.
获胜者将赢得一个其他选手没有的
The winner will gain a very special advantage
特殊奖励
over the other contestants.
这是我的主意 詹姆斯听了想要试试
This is my concept that James has agreed to try.
希望你们能喜欢
I hope you like it.
叫做
It's called
"一些卢瑟知道的东西 但想看看你们知道不知道"
"things Luther knows, but wants to see if you know."
是电影"帮助"！
The movie "The Help"!
好的 第一个问题
Okay. First question.
太阳系中哪个行星
Which planet in our solar system
是被小行星撞击最多的?
gets hit with the most asteroids?
我不知道!
I have no idea!
我也不知道
I have no idea, either.
我们一样的
We are the same.
你知道答案才能按铃
Only buzz in if you know the answer.
好吧
Okay.
在珍妮・杰克逊
Who was that guy
的黑与白Mv里
in the black-and-white Janet Jackson video
在沙漠里的半圆上做平衡的男子是谁?
in the desert who balanced on that big half-circle thing?
我不知道!
I have no idea!
我也不知道
I don't know, either.
- Djimon Hounsou. - 我知道的!
- Djimon Hounsou. - I knew that!
詹姆斯在我有机会回答之前就说了
James answered before I had a chance.
没法证明
Tough to prove.
好的 让我们继续
Okay, let's wrap this round up.
回答了下一个问题的人
Whoever answers this next question
将赢得游戏
will win the game.
什么电影...
What film...
电影"帮助"
The movie "The Help."
完全正确!
Absolutely correct!
- 克洛伊赢得了游戏 - 太好了
- Chloe wins the game.
- Yes!
Minny在派里放了便便(电影帮助内容)
Minny put poop in the pie.
该死 我拿错卡了
Damn it. I took out the wrong card.
Chole 作为游戏赢家
Chloe, as winner of this game,
你将赢得...
you will receive the valuable...
头脑叉子
mind fork.
头脑叉子将扭转局势
In a much-needed twist,
它将给你权限
the mind fork will allow you access
用一件设计好的私人信息
to one piece of personal information
来使一位参赛者大吃一惊
designed to blow one of the contestant's minds.
我现在要给阿朱
I give it to June right now.
好的!
Okay!
非常好 我喜欢
All right. I like it.
阿朱 使你大吃一惊的信息是
June, your mind-blowing piece of information is,
马克
Mark...
迷上你了
has a crush on you.
哇哦
Ooh.
你的精神刚刚肯定分叉了
You just got mind forked.
什么?
What?
不可能
No.
马克没有喜欢上我
Mark doesn't have a crush on me.
你们这些家伙肯定是
You guys made that up
把这个当作节目的小插曲
as part of a twist in the game.
我想 对吗?
I mean, right?
哦 精神叉起作用了!
Ooh, the mind fork is working!
嘿 你把钱包落在Beans了
Hey. Uh, you left your wallet at Beans.
啊 还真是
Ah. Yes, I did.
故意的吗? 很难说哦
On purpose? Tough to prove.
重点是你现在在这了
Point is, you're here.
阿朱 马克来了
June. Mark's here.
嗨 马克
Hey, Mark.
慌乱的马克
Funky Mark.
我正要走了
I was just leavin'.
出门 下四层楼
Out the door, four-on-the-floor.
好吧 我们 我们明天还要
Okay. Uh, are... are we still on
一起看"五月的春天"的大结局吗?
for the "Spring Into May" finale tomorrow?
当然!
Yeah!
讨厌!
Nasty!
拍屁股
Buttocks.
精神分叉
Mind forked.
我混乱了
I was flustered.
如果马克真的喜欢我
If Mark really did have a crush on me...
对了 这可真是一个不小的"如果"
which, by the way, is a big "if"...
我现在不可能去想那个
I couldn't think about that right then.
我必须集中在丹尼尔身上
I had to focus on Daniel
准备迎接下一个挑战
and the next challenge.
我们见了丹尼尔他那伟大的姑姑
We were meeting Daniel's great aunt.
我们想听她说她认为
We had to get her to say which girl
对丹尼尔来说什么样的女孩才是最好的
she thought was best for Daniel.
但是我高兴的是可以和克洛伊分一个肉馅饼
But I was just happy to split a potpie with Chloe.
你什么意思 我们不能分一个?
What do you mean, we can't split it?
小姐 这是肉馅饼
Ma'am. It's a pot pie.
里面的馅都会散出来的
All the stuff inside it will spill out.
这和你有什么关系呢?
Why is it just problems with you?
丹尼尔真的是个很棒的男人
So Daniel seems like a really great guy,
他非常爱您
and he loves you very much.
我喜欢您的 面罩
I like your... face hat.
我很珍惜更好得了解他的机会
I'd really like the chance to get to know him better,
- 所以如果您可以 - 好啦
- so if you could just... - Okay.
准备好接受又一个小插曲了吗?
Are you ready for the next twist?
现在遇到了双重精神分叉
Because here comes the double mind fork.
丹尼尔
Daniel.
爱吉姑姑 你没事吧?
Aunt Aggie, are you okay?
你不能吃这的东西
You can't eat anything here.
你们两个是怎么回事?
What is wrong with you two?
我 我接到了詹姆斯・范德・ 比克的电话
I... I get a phone call from James Van Der Beek,
他告诉我你们把我姑姑
telling me that you stole my great aunt
从养老院里面偷走了?
from her retirement home?
我 我都不知道你们两个居然认识
I... I had no idea you two even knew each other.
现在我发现你们正在玩着
And now I find out you're playing
什么无聊的真实约会的游戏?
some sick, real-life dating game?
嗨 我是洛冰 我也是竞争者
Hi. I'm Robin. I'm competing for you, too.
另外说下 我不是喜欢你
P.S., I'm not attracted to you.
丹尼尔 我很抱歉
Daniel, I'm so sorry.
我以为这是唯一的
I thought this was the only way
可以了解你的方法
that I'd have a chance to get to know you.
好吧 你太疯狂了
Well, then, you're crazy.
太疯狂了 你们都有病
This is crazy. You're all insane.
哦 我的天
Oh, my gosh.
我真不应该听你的
I should have never listened to you.
我喜欢他 现在都毁了
I like this guy, and now it's all ruined,
- 全是因为你 - 嘿
- because of you. - Hey.
我也喜欢他
I liked him, too.
只是因为我先喜欢他
Only because I liked him.
洛冰在这是因为你
And Robin's here because of you,
而詹姆斯在这是因为他那愚蠢的游戏
and James is here because of his stupid game.
是很蠢
It is stupid.
对不起 詹姆斯
I'm sorry, James,
但是这游戏真的很无聊
but it is a dumb game.
没有任何意义
This isn't connected to anything.
哦 太可笑了
Oh, this is ridiculous.
我不应该让你说服我去做任何事的
I should have never let you talk me into something
既骗人又低劣
so dishonest and mean.
好啦 爱吉姑姑 现在没事啦
Okay, Aunt Aggie, everything is fine now.
哇 这儿闻上去有股坚果味
Blah! Whoa. It smells like nuts in here.
怎么回事? 我想我已经说得很清楚了
What? I thought I made myself clear.
我不想和你们有任何瓜葛
I don't want anything to do with you.
首先 我不相信你
First of all, I don't believe you.
其次 我不是为我自己来的 我是为了阿朱
And second, I'm not here for me. I'm here for June.
听着 她一点都不想参加这个鬼游戏
Look, she didn't want anything to do with this stupid game.
她只是想用正常的无聊的方式和你约会
She just wanted to date you in a normal, boring way,
而我和詹姆斯不想让她那样
and James and I didn't let that happen.
所以你应该再给她一次机会
So she deserves another chance.
不要因为我们做的事对她生气
Don't be mad at her for what we did.
听着 我很抱歉
Look, I'm sorry,
但是阿朱可以不这样做的
but June didn't have to go along with it
如果她真的不想
if she didn't want to.
现在请离开
Now please leave
我会忘掉发生的一切的
so I can forget this ever happened.
什么?
What?
哦 那东西说话了?
Oh, that thing talks?
阿朱是个好姑娘 去找她
June's a good girl. Go to her.
你能相信那个老太太说"去找她"了吗?
Can you believe the old lady said "go to her"?
我是说 这节目太棒了
I mean... that's great television.
我不知道卢瑟在说什么
I don't know what Luther's talking about.
我的节目太神奇了
My show's incredible.
马克
Mark,
第一手的好消息
I got a hit on my hands.
所有的插曲和曲折
All the twists and turns...
精神分叉真的把整个节目提升了一个层次
the mind fork really took the whole game to another level
当我告诉阿朱你喜欢她的时候
when I told June you had a crush on her.
你告诉阿朱我喜欢她?
You told June I have a crush on her?
你怎么能这么做?
How could you do that?
哦 伙计
Oh, dude...
这对我的节目有好处
it helped my game.
哦 现在一团乱 哥们!
Well, that's messed up, man!
你的节目甚至还不是真的
Your game isn't even real.
我 她.. 她怎么说的?
I... wh... what did she say?
实际上 她没说什么
Well, not much, really.
我是说 她很快地转回到丹尼尔的事情上了
I mean, she got back on Daniel pretty quick.
她没事
She's fine.
哦 很好 我也没事
Oh, good, 'cause I'm fine, too.
我们今晚本来要一起看"五月的春天"的大结局的
We're supposed to watch the finale of "Spring Into May"
现在也没问题啦
together tonight, and that'll be fine... too.
看见没? 人人都是赢家
See? Everybody wins
一切尽在詹姆斯・范德・ 比克出品的节目
on "James Van Der Beek presents:
约会... 交换... 细节... 叉子
Date... swap... trivia... fork."
我还没想好名字 我想不出合适的名字马克
I don't have it yet. I don't have the name, Mark.
我得出去跑两圈
I'm gonna go for a run.
丹尼尔 你怎么来了?
Daniel. What are you doing here?
克洛伊和爱吉姨妈
Chloe and Aunt Aggie
说服我前来再给你一次机会
convinced me to give you another chance.
克洛伊? 我家克洛伊?
Chloe? My Chloe?
我当时很郁闷
I was upset.
我不想成为别人什么游戏中的赌注
I don't appreciate being a pawn in someone else's game.
但是我喜欢你 你看起来像是个好人
But I like you, and you seem like a good person.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我再不参加什么游戏了
No more games.
我保证 未来只有你我二人
Just me and you, I promise.
进屋吧 我正好要开始看这季
Come in. I'm actually watching the season finale
May的又一春的大结局(双关这个要解释不)
of "Spring Into May,"
May马上就要给出她的黄金弹簧了
and May is about to give out her final golden spring.
我知道是个脑残节目 但是很好看
I know it's stupid, but it's fun.
来个卷饼?
Do you want a burrito?
不 不要 我讨厌卷饼
Oh, God, no. I hate burritos.
怎么会有人喜欢
Why would I like a food
把所有的料都包起来看不到的食物?
that hides all its ingredients from view?
这就好比 你买了双鞋
It's like, let's buy a pair of shoes
但是只把它们放鞋盒里
and just keep 'em in the box.
这不是一回事
It's really not the same thing.
就是一回事
It kind of is.
不是 实际上...
No, it's actually...
这两件事...
it's not even close to...
我为什么要替卷饼说话?
you know, why am I defending burritos?
再说下去节目就要结束了
We are missing the show.
May 现在
So, May,
是你好好想清楚的时候了
you've had a chance to think it all through.
你会选择谁?
Who's it gonna be?
做这个动作其实挺好玩的 为结局做铺垫
It's kind of fun if you do this, get into it.
这看起来很怪
That's pretty weird.
他能否改变May的心意?
Could he have warned May any differently?
所以这是她男朋友还是别的什么人?
So is that her boyfriend or something?
不是 那是... 那是节目主持人
No, that... that's the host.
一开始上场24位男嘉宾 然后慢慢减少到...
It started as 24 men, then down to...
所以 这姑娘是很有名还是...
So is she, like, a famous person or...
她... 她就是以普通姑娘
She's... she's a regular girl.
你能别说话么? 我听不清节目了
But can you just be quiet, though, so we can hear?
得 知道了
Right. Got it.
最终决定她选择...
Make her final decision as to who...
嘿 你除了卷饼还有别的吃的不?
Hey, do you have anything else to eat besides burritos?
别是蛋卷就行了
And obviously not an egg roll,
你知道的... 一样的问题
'cause... same issue.
稍后即将播出
Coming up next,
我们看看最终她将选择哪位幸运儿 不要走开 马上回来
we'll see which lucky guy she chooses.Stay tuned.
抱歉 丹尼尔
I'm sorry, Daniel.
我突然想到要去个地方
I just realized there's somewhere else I need to be.
啥?
What?
我只是不觉得我们会有结果
I just don't think we're gonna work out.
哈罗!
Hi!
哈罗! 你们这对小鸳鸯
Well, hello, lovebirds.
不 我们不是小鸳鸯
No. No lovebirds.
我们不会成功的
It's not gonna work out.
但是我很高兴你找他谈过了
But thank you so much for having a chat with him.
你真是个好人
That was very cool of you.
我就是好人
I'm pretty cool.
所以...
So...
你想找点事做做吗?
you wanna do stuff?
什么事?
What do you mean?
你懂得 那种... 事
You know, like... stuff.
我滴个神啊
Oh, my God.
就算没有阿朱和我抢
I wanna hook up with you
我都愿意和你约一炮
even though June doesn't want to anymore.
这就是成长啊
That's growth.
这是成长 我真为你骄傲啊 克洛伊
That is growth. I'm proud of you, Chloe.
谢谢啦 上帝
Thanks, God!
我没有打扰到你吧
I hope it's okay that I'm here.
当然... 当然不打扰
Yeah. Of... of course.
没有你我看不下去大结局
I couldn't watch the finale without you.
感觉都不一样了
It just wouldn't be the same.
马克 你愿意接受
Mark, will you accept...
我的银色卷饼吗?
my silver burrito?
我愿意
I will. Yes.
我错过啥了没?
Did I miss anything?
有 大概十四条的衣物柔顺剂的广告
Yeah, like, 14 commercials for fabric softener.
May还没最后一次给出她的黄金弹簧?
So May hasn't given out her final golden spring?
还没 节目不停地在拖
No. They drag these things out so much.
让他们拖吧
Yeah. It's okay.
本来我就不想着节目结束
I kind of never want it to end.
我也是
Yeah. Me, too.
别忘了收看九月播出的
Don't forget to tune in this September
爱上Autumn（又是个双关 这个也不知道怎么体现）预告片
for the premiere of "Fall Into Autumn."
最终我都没提
So I didn't bring up
马克对我有意思 这档子事
the whole "Mark having a crush on me" thing
我觉得他准备好了自己会说的
'cause I figured he could tell me when he's ready.
目前 我就专心享受和基友及其看节目
For now, I just enjoyed watching the show with my friend.
以上就是全部的经过了
And that's pretty much it.
我一点都不想知道以上这些信息
I literally didn't need any of that information.
一点不关心你们中任何一个
None of it. From any of you.
我让你们过来只是因为我想了解
You're all here because I wanna know
丹尼尔的姨妈发生过什么
what happened to Daniel's aunt.
Agnes Whipple现在在哪儿?
Now where is Agnes Whipple?
丹尼尔送她回了养老院
Daniel took her back to the nursing home,
然后我们就没见过她了
and that's the last time we saw her.
她现在不在那里
Well, she's not there now.
Agnes Whipple失踪了
Agnes Whipple is missing.
你们这群畜生把她藏哪儿了?!
Where is she, you monsters?!
这种关系不太正常啊 是吧?
That's a weird relationship, right?
你不觉得他们走的太近了?
I mean, they're way too close.